ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Western States Region Records
1940-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/115
96 cubic feet
96 linear ft.
Records (documents), photographs.
Contains records of the office of the Western States Region's constitutive departments, namely Political and Education, Organizing, Legal Services, and Accounting and Miscellaneous Services. Contains an extensive series of papers from Cornelius Wall (Director, Western States Region), Max Wolf (Director, Political and Education Department), Ralph Smith (Director, Organizing Department) and Smith's successor, Meyer Silverstein (Director, Organizing Department). Also contains reports of house calls to prospective ILGWU members in records from the Organizing Department (boxes 80, 81, 87) and Cornelius Wall (box 94). Includes substantial records of arbitrations, cases before the National Labor Relations Board, and company files. Dispersed throughout the records are files on all of the joint boards and district councils (Los Angeles Joint Board, San Francisco Joint Board, Arizona-Utah District Council, Southern California District Council) as well as individual locals (in Oregon and Washington) that fell under the purview of the Western States. However, activities in California are more fully represented than other areas of the Western States Region.
5520621
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Z. Guttendorf, August 11, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The ILGWU's Western States Region covered Arizona, California, Oregon, Utah, and Washington. After its formation in 1980, the Pacific Northwest was part of the Western States Region. Likewise, the Southwest District Council's was established in 1988 and was included in the Western States Region.
Israel Feinberg was the ILGWU's general representative on the west coast from 1933 to 1939. Louis Levy then served in that role from 1939 until his resignation in 1950. Hyman Langer succeeded Levy, but then died suddenly in 1951. Samuel Otto was Los Angeles and Pacific Coast Region Director from 1952 to 1970. Cornelius Wall was appointed Western States Region Director in 1970, and retired in 1986. Steve Nutter was the final ILGWU Western States Region Director, beginning in that position in 1986 and continuing after the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995.
Mattie Jackson was Pacific Northwest District Council Manager from 1980 to 1990. Katie Quan succeeded her in that position. Antonio Orea was Southwest District Council Manager from 1988 to 1995.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Western State Region are large and extensive, but there are evident subjects and themes that emerge in the records. The largest portion of the collection mainly deals with company files from the region. These are identified by individual garment firm and include agreements, negotiations, correspondence, and arbitration cases and decisions. In fact, there are substantial records of arbitrations and cases before the National Labor Relations Board. The folders of Master Files (1947-1975) lists for each year, firm, case number and disposition type, as well as the decision of the Impartial Chairman for each case.
Numerous ILGWU departments are represented, including Research, Union Label, Legislative, Death Benefit, Education, National Retirement Fund, and Health and Welfare, as well as the General Executive Board and national convention. There are the records of the office of the Western State Region's constitutive departments, in particular Political and Education, Organizing, Legal Services, and Accounting and Miscellaneous Services. Committees of the Western States Region include meeting minutes from the Appeals, Executive, Vacation and Health and Welfare Fund, and Retirement Fund Committees. Administrative records of the region reflect elections, procedures, the governance of region, and financial information such as bills, ledgers, the Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund and unemployment insurance, cash receipts, deposits, and accounts.
Correspondence occurs with other unions and organizations (Teamsters, United Farm Workers, the AFL-CIO) and manufacturer associations. Extensive papers and correspondence are from Cornelius Wall (Director, Western States Region), Max Wolf (Director, Political and Education Department), Ralph Smith (Director, Organizing Department) and Smith's successor, Meyer Silverstein (Director, Organizing Department).
Throughout the records are files on the other joint boards, district councils and locals that were under the jurisdiction of the Western States Region, including the San Francisco Joint Board, Los Angeles Joint Board, Arizona-Utah District Council, and Southern California District Council and numerous locals in Oregon and Washington. Information on individuals can be found in personal files that on members who filed complaints against companies, and reports of house calls to prospective members from the Organizing Department.
Subjects reflected in the records that could be explored in-depth include politics. There is substantial information on political campaign contributions, correspondence with representatives, especially on Senate Bills and labor laws that affected the garment industry and workers in the region. Additionally there are meeting minutes and testimony of the General Relief Review Committee, a group appointed by the Los Angeles County Board of supervisors to review the Los Angeles General Assistance program and make recommendations for improvement.
The 1970s and 1980s saw a return of sweatshop conditions and the employment of undocumented workers. The Immigration and Naturalization Service began conducting factory raids to question employees at work of their citizenship status and arrest any illegals they found working in the factory. An important case involved the Southern California Davis Pleating Company in which federal agents conducted "surveys" in January and September of 1977, with probable cause that the factory employed illegal aliens. Agents were stationed at factory exits while others moved through the shop questioning employees at their work stations. This incident led to the U.S. Supreme Court case of the Immigration and Naturalization Service et al. v. Delgado et al. and whether factors raids deprive workers of their Constitutional rights. Records on the INS, immigration raids, and the Southern California Davis Pleating Co. are well represented in the collection. Another subject contained in the collection is on plant closures and runaway plants. These records include legislative hearings on plant closures, with compiled case reports, studies, articles and literature providing background information on the problem of plant closures and also the trend of "runaway plants" relocating in Mexico.
While the Western States Region covered Arizona, Oregon, Utah and Washington, activities in California are more fully represented than other areas of the region.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/046: ILGWU Los Angeles Joint Board Records 5780/065: ILGWU San Francisco Joint Board Records 5780/207: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records 5780/207 P: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Photographs
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- New York (State); Women's clothing industry -- Illinois -- Chicago; Women's clothing industry -- California -- San Francisco; Women's clothing industry -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia; Women's clothing industry -- Washington (State) -- Seattle; Women's clothing industry -- Ohio -- Cincinnati; Women's clothing industry -- Manitoba -- Winnipeg; Women's clothing industry -- Connecticut; Women's clothing industry -- Massachusetts; Women's clothing industry -- California -- Los Angeles; Women's clothing industry -- Canada; Women's clothing industry -- Wyoming; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Illinois -- Chicago; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- California -- San Francisco; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Washington (State) -- Seattle; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Ohio -- Cincinnati; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Manitoba -- Winnipeg; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Connecticut; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Massachusetts; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- California -- Los Angeles; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Canada; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Wyoming; Clothing workers -- United States; Clothing workers -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Illinois -- Chicago; Clothing workers -- California -- San Francisco; Clothing workers -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia; Clothing workers -- Washington (State) -- Seattle; Clothing workers -- Connecticut; Clothing workers -- Massachusetts; Clothing workers -- Ohio -- Cincinnati; Clothing workers -- Manitoba -- Winnipeg; Industrial relations -- United States; Industrial relations -- Canada; Industrial relations -- New York (State); Industrial relations -- Illinois -- Chicago; Industrial relations -- California; Industrial relations -- Washington (State); Industrial relations -- Ohio -- Cincinnati; Industrial relations -- Manitoba -- Winnipeg; Industrial relations -- Connecticut; Industrial relations -- Massachusetts; Industrial relations -- California -- Los Angeles; Industrial relations -- Wyoming; Nagler, Isidore, 1895-; Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union; International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Local 15 (Philadelphia, Pa.); International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Retiree Service Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Local 50 (Philadelphia, Pa.); International Ladies' Garment Worker's Union. Local 205, Dress Cutter's Union; International Ladies' Garment Worker's Union. Local 315, (Montreal (Quebec)); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Western States Region; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Bonnaz, Embroideries, Tucking, Pleating and; Allied Crafts Union, Local 66; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Chicago Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Children's Wear and Allied Workers' Union, Local 91-105; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Cloak Out-of-Town Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Convention; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Educational Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Embroidery, Belt and Allied Workers' Union, Local 66-40; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. General Executive Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. International Relations Dept.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 1 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 2 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 5 (Chicago, Ill.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 8 (San Francisco, Calif.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 9 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 11 (Brownsville, N.Y.); International Ladies Garment Workers Union.Local 15 (Philadelphia, Pa.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 17 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 19; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 20 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 21 (Chicago, Ill.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 22 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 28 (Seattle, Wash.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 30 (Cincinnati, Ohio); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 32 (Winnipeg, Man.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 33 (Bridgeport, Conn.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 34 (Bridgeport, Conn.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 35 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 37 (Cleveland, Ohio); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 38 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 39-40 (New Haven, Conn.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 41 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 43 (Worcester, Mass.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 44 (Chicago, Ill.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 45 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 48 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 49 (Boston, Mass.); International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Local 50 (Philadelphia, Pa.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 52 (Los Angeles, Calif.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 61; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 62 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 64 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 66 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 80 (Boston, Mass.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 89 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 91 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 105 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 112; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 117; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 155 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 262 (Montreal (Quebec)); International Ladies' Garment Worker's Union. Local 315, (Montreal (Quebec)); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 342; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 438; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 584; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 592; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 205, Dress Cutter's Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New England Region; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New York Cloak Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New York Dress Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New York Joint Board of the Dressmakers' Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Northeast Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Research Dept; International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Retiree Service Department; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. San Francisco Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Union Health Center; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Welfare and Health Benefits Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Workers' Education Bureau; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Wyoming Valley District; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Unity House
5520621
- Mister Herbert, 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mister Herbert, 1963-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mayfair Coat Company, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mode O'Sports Incorporated, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mutual Industries, 1968-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Non-Association Members, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1953-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mr. Pleat, Incorporated, 1960-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Patricia Belt Company, 1958-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Park Pleating Company, 1966-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rayson Castings and Manufacturing, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Robbins Button Company, 1958-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Robin Sportswear, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Robert Kaufman, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Roxy Zipper Company, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Davis Pleating Company, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Variations Limited, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Smart Modes, 1957-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Schnell Sportswear, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Stephanie Fashion, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Standard Bias, 1958-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Stitch Craft, 1958-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Star Button Company, 1958-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Superior Pleating and Stitching Company, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Harold Swartz, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Steal Manufacturing Company, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Superior Bias Binding, 1958-1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Tanne Apparel, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Universal Belt of California Incorporated, 1964-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Venus of California, 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Sportswear Vacation and Retirement, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Zel Sportswear, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Mahler Belts, Incorporated, 1953-1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Mahler Sales, Incorporated, 1958-1975 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Messerman Sportswear, 1949-1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Anna Myers Sportswear, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Antoinette Fashion Company, 1957-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Joint Review Board, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Ferrara of California, 1949-1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Calbrooke. Incorporated, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Caliday, 1951-1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Atelier-7, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Smart Modes, 1949-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Jo. L. Fashions, 1964-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Jo. L. Fashions, 1965-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Daniel, Jay of California, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Loring Corporation, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miss Scott, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Campioni, Incorporated, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Caldon Fashions, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- C & C Sportswear, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Smart Maid Garment Company, 1953-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Blakeslee Manufacturing, 1960-1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- George Brandel (Vikki Fashions), 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bar-Craft of California, 1955-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Amdur De Marco Company, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Abbate Originals, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Joe Accordino, Incorporated, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Dumas Brothers, 1961-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Din, Kathi, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- D'Andre of California, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Braemar Coat Company, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Bouquet Fashions, 1965-1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Tejay Sportswear (Miss Kari Sue), 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Stanley Nelson, Incorporated, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Vanguard Fashions, 1958-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- BelAir Belts, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- B&H Apparel, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- H&M Sportswear, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Carol Lee Fashions, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Starline Coat Company, 1953-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Fashion Craft, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Robert B. Sagman, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Tabak of California, 1948-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Star-Glo Formals, 1956-1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- W.S.R. Corporation [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- W.S.R. Corporation [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Smart Modes, 1964-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Smart Modes of California, 1957-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Jo. L. Fashions, 1964-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Victory Embroidery Company, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Alexander's of California, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Gloria Manufacturing Company, 1948-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Merrill Sharpio of California, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jewel, Incorporated, 1956-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Elnar of California, 1955-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Andrea Frocks, Bitmore Frocks, and I.M. Fashions, 1948-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- A. & A. Stitching, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Advance Pleating, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- L.A. Dress and Sportswear Joint Board, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- L.C. Mae of Hollywood, 1965-1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Local 266, 1948-1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Sportswear, 1953-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Jolie Belts Incorporated, 1957-1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Pleating Company, 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- K-Mart Apparel [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- K-Mart Apparel [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Kathy Sue of California, 1966-1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Kiku's Sewing Company, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Knits International, 1970-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Krieger L. Bias Binding, 1957-1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- L.A. Pleating, Stitching and Button, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Los Angeles Embroidery, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- El Jo Styles, Incorporated, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Fisher Dress Manufacturing, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Emgee Novelty, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Fels Company, 1954-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Frank Lee of California, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Harry Goldberg Belt Company, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Hartfield-Zody, 1971-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Hollywood Leather, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Holly Stores Incorporated, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Hedman Hedders, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Jennifer, Incorporated, 1964-1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- A&A Sportswear, 1957-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Acme Belt Company, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Adrian Belt Company, 1949-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Albert's, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Alfar Imports, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Amedo Belts, 1956-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- American Girl Coat Company, 1970-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Anjac Fashions, 1959-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Annetta of California, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Aquarius or Arizona, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Arden Division, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Arden Division of Lucky Stores, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Arlin Belt Company, 1964-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Arrow Belt Company, 1949-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Art Craft Tucking and Stitching, 1958-1965 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Associated Lace Company, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Atelier-7, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)